A Guide to the Papers of Michael J. Stolee, 1964 to 2009
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- School Desegregation Cases
  - Tennessee 1972 to 2001
    This sub-series includes Chattanooga for 1973; Jackson from 1988-1990 and 1998-2001; Knoxville from 1972 and 1991; and Nashville from 1996 to 1998.
    - Chattanooga 1973 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Jackson 1999-2001 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Jackson 1998-2001 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Jackson – Fees and Expenses 1988-90 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Jackson Madison County School System “Vision for the Future” 1999 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Jackson -- News Clippings 1997 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Jackson – Transcripts I 2000 (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Jackson – Transcripts II 2000 (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Knoxville 1972, 1991 (Box-folder 19:12)
    - Knoxville -- News Clippings 1991 (Box-folder 19:13)
    - Nashville 1996-98 (Box-folder 19:14)
  - Texas 1978 to 1990
    Texas. This sub-series includes Austin from 1989 to 1990; Beaumont for 1981; and Dallas from 1978 to 1981.
    - Austin 1989 (Box-folder 19:15)
    - Austin -- Testimony 1990 (Box-folder 19:16)
    - Beaumont 1981 (Box-folder 19:17)
    - Dallas 1978-81 (Box-folder 19:18)
  - Virginia 1969 to 1994
    This sub-series includes Lynchburg for 1970; Newport News for 1994; Norfolk from 1969-1971; Richmond from 1970 to 1972; and Roanoke for 1970.
    - Lynchburg – News Clippings 1970 (Box-folder 19:19)
    - Newport News 1994 (Box-folder 19:20)
    - Norfolk – News Clippings 1969-71 (Box-folder 19:21)
    - Richmond 1970-72 (Box-folder 19:22)
    - Roanoke – News Clippings 1970 (Box-folder 19:23)
  - Washington 1979, 1989
    This sub-series includes Seattle for 1979 and 1989.
    - Seattle News Clippings 1979, 1989 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Wisconsin 1975 to 1996
    This sub-series includes Burlington for 1985; Florence from 1995-1996; Green Bay for 1994; and Milwaukee from 1975 to 1988 and 1996.
    - Burlington Deposition 1985 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Florence – Fees and Expenses 1995-96 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Green Bay Catholic 1994 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Milwaukee 1984-86, 1996 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Milwaukee Deposition I 1986 (Box-folder 20:6)
    - Milwaukee Deposition II 1986 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Milwaukee News Clippings 1975-1988 (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Milwaukee – “Racial Desegregation in the Milwaukee Public Schools” by Michael J. Stolee undated (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 32 undated (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 33 undated (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 34 undated (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 35 undated (Box-folder 21:1)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 36 undated (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 37 undated (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 38 undated (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 39 undated (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 40 undated (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 41 undated (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 42 undated (Box-folder 22:3)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 43 undated (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Milwaukee Testimony: Volume 44 undated (Box-folder 22:5)
- Other Media. undated
  This series is broken into three sub-series.
  - Floppy Disks undated
    This series contains eight floppy discs related to cases that Dr. Stolee worked with. Materials are arranged alphabetically and are not dated.
    - Benton Harbor undated (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Calendars by Case undated (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Cases undated (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Cases (back-up) undated (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Case Histories Copy undated (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Case Histories (back-up) undated (Box-folder 23:6)
    - Kansas City undated (Box-folder 23:7)
    - Kansas City 2 undated (Box-folder 23:8)
  - Court Sketches undated
    This series contains three court artist sketches of Dr. Stolee testifying in an undisclosed court.
    - Artist's Court Sketch undated (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Artists' Court Sketch undated (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Artists' Court Sketch undated (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Posters 1974
    This series contains a poster for the School Master’s Kiwanis Luncheon in Atlantic City, New Jersey from February 25, 1974.
    - School Masters Kiwanis Luncheon, Atlantic City, NJ February 25, 1974 (Box-folder 24:4)